wildspark.me 2017-10-01

# WildSpark | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the use of your information provided by you and/or collected by us when you use any of the services provided by Synereo, Inc. (with its affiliates, **“Synereo”** ) consisting of the websites available at [https://www.WildSpark.me](https://www.wildspark.me/), [http://www.synereo.com](http://www.synereo.com/), and its network of websites, software applications, or any other products or services offered by Synereo from time to time (the **“Synereo Services”** ). When you use our services, you’ll share some information with us.

We are posting this privacy policy in order for you to know what information we collect, how we use it, whom we share it with, and the choices we give you to control, access, and update your information. If after reading this policy you still have any questions about your privacy or any part of our Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](mailto:Hello@synereo.com).

**What Information We Collect**

We collect several types of information and may use each kind differently as we will detail below:

**Information You Submit to Us**

When you interact with our services, we collect the information that you choose to share with us. For example, when you set up an account, we need to collect a few important details about you, such as: a unique username, a password, an email address, a phone number, date of birth, etc. We may decide to collect additional (or less) information in the future. Other services may require you to provide us with a debit or credit card number and its associated account information.

Additional information might be collected when you contact our support or communicate with us in any other way.

**Information We Get When You Use Our Services**

When you use our services, we collect information about which of those services you’ve used and how you’ve used them, which pages you visited, etc.

Here’s a more detailed explanation of the types of information we may collect, now or in the future:

  1. information about your activity through our services (e.g. access times, pages viewed, IP address, , etc.)
  2. information about how you interact with other users.
  3. information about any content you choose to provide us, or share through our services and the use that other users are doing with such content.
  4. device-specific information, such as the hardware model, operating system version, advertising identifier, unique application identifiers, unique device identifiers, browser type, language, wireless network, and mobile network information (including the mobile phone number).
  5. information about your location.
  6. information collected by cookies and other technologies (please see our Cookies Usage Policy).

**Information We Collect from Third Parties**

We may collect information that other users provide about you when they use our services. For example, if another user allows us to collect information from their device phonebook—and you’re one of that user’s contacts—we may combine the information we collect from that user’s phonebook with other information we have collected about you. We may also obtain information from other companies that are owned or operated by us, or any other third-party sources, and combine that with the information we collect through our services.

**How We Use Information**

We use the information we collect for several purposes, including for operating our services, improving and personalizing them, securing them and providing you with better services. We also use the information we collect to communicate with you, respond to inquiries or share information about our services. Another use is protecting you and your account in order to prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity.

**How We Share the Information We collect**

We may share information about you with other users (by allowing users to view you profile, follow your activity, etc.), with our partners, affiliates, service providers and with the public. Please note that we will never share personal identifiable information with others without your consent other than for legal purposes (such as in case of a court order, under any applicable law, in a dispute between us, for protecting our other users, etc.). We might also share your information with third parties as part of a merger or acquisition or other material transactions entered into by Synereo.

**Third-Party Content and Integrations**

The services may contain third-party links and search results, include third-party integrations, or offer a co-branded or third-party-branded service, whereby you may be providing information (including personal information) directly to the third party, us, or both. You acknowledge and agree that we are not responsible for how those third parties collect or use your information and encourage you to review the privacy policies of every third-party website or service that you visit or use.

**Analytics and Advertising Services Provided by Others**

We may let other companies use cookies, web beacons, and similar tracking technologies on our services. These companies may collect information about how you use our services and other websites and online services over time and across different services. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand your online activity.

**How you can Control Your Information**

You may access and update most of the personal information we collect about you by visiting the setting section of our services. However, we may reject a request for a number of reasons, including, for example, that the request risks the privacy of other users, requires technical efforts that are disproportionate to the request, is repetitive, or is unlawful. You can also send us requests in this subject to support@wildspark.me.

**Revisions to the Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, at our discretion and will inform you if we do that by revising the date at the top of the Privacy Policy we post or we may provide you with additional notice.
